hey what's up Jeremiah Kowski here and
today I want to talk about Evergreen
offers and how you can get the same
results that you would from a live
launch webinar or Challenge from your
Evergreen offers is the right way to do
so something that I'm teaching my
clients that we're working with hundreds
of clients on in their businesses that
we've actually gotten a ton of results
with with some of our clients as well as
our own business and how you can as well
now again for those of you that I have
not met yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski
for the last 21 almost 22 years now I've
been in the online marketing and sales
space for coaches course creators
seminars we built multiple businesses
over the $20 million a year profit Mark
and I want to show you if you're just
starting out what to do to get more
clients to make more money and to
actually have stuff work for you again
as you can tell I'm kind of more down
toe more raw more real not as polished
and super produced as most people that
are in this industry that's kind of part
of my branding as far as that goes so
what we're going to be talking about
here today is how to make things
Evergreen now I believe that live
launches are incredible and you can get
a lot of value out of them I think that
for people that are just starting out
they're really great because it's
something that you can build towards
something that you can work towards to
get more clients in your business let's
say that you build a webinar you get
people in front of it you can present
something to them and get them to buy
your programs or you can do a 5-day
challenge I also think that they have a
great place inside of an evergreen
system where you don't do them as often
but you do them for people that want
just a a little bit more personal touch
and it allows you to remove a lot of the
sales calls or live other elements in
there to get more clients okay here's
the reason why live is amazing and
people love it is because you get that
Personal Touch that personal experience
however it's a drain on your time and
it's exhausting and going live with
content uh with challenges with webinars
with funnels and having to put another
one out there and another one out there
comes exhausting and it's not the kind
of lifestyle that we signed up for in
our businesses as coaches or mentors
plus it pulls you out of your zone of
Genius to have to do these things and so
what I want to break down for you is
what I believe and what is working right
now to go Evergreen with everything but
still get the same kind of result that
you get from live launching challenges
or webinars okay so here's the reason
the difference is when you do live the
benefit is
urgency and scarcity and I think that's
really the two main benefits of anything
that's live is because when something is
not live I mean this video right here
not live just statistically most of the
people who started watching this video
haven't made it to the 2 minute and 48
second Mark that you're watching right
now because there's no urgency or reason
for them to do so there's other videos
that they can go watch there's a lot of
things vying for their attention so for
that reason when things aren't live you
get less people actually watching it
overall however there's more
accessibility there's a lower percentage
of people I mean watching it overall but
you can actually get more people total
let me explain that so you might have uh
200 people on live and 50% might watch
all of it but you might for Evergreen
you might be able to get 2,000 people
and 10% watch it so that's actually more
than 200 it's a lower percentage but
it's more than 200 so that would be two
200 people well it's actually is 200
it's 200 right here whereas this is only
100 so the idea is it's actually double
what the live would be now again 2,000
people that might sign up or register or
something like that yes there might be a
large percentage that are not going to
consume the content they're not going to
go through it but Evergreen has this
beautiful factor that you don't have to
be there to be selling to people now the
urgency does disappear so we what we
have to do is we have to learn how to
bring those things back into it and
there's a couple of ways that you can
bring the similar urgency that you get
from live launching or webinars into
Evergreen and here's here's how I like
to do it and I'm going to explain this
to you is what we do is we figure out
what is one specific area that we can
help our clients with and we create a
sequence like
this we create a lead
magnet that gets people on our email
list from there
they watch a piece of video content and
then in that piece of video content they
get sold the program as far as that goes
okay we also
have video content in the form of short
form this would be Instagram we also
have long form video content and we have
emails that we send out so all of this
is leading people to our lead magnet
right here even if somebody is already
on our email list we're going to be
sending them to our lead magnet and
that's one of the things that I know is
a lot of people they're like well
they're already on the email list why do
I need to send them to sign up for
something a lead magnet is basically
some piece of value that you're offering
somebody that they got to give you their
name and email address for so they're
signing up with their name and email
address and then you're delivering that
value right here to them and in exchange
for delivering that value you get an
opportunity to sell what you're offering
but here's the problem the urgency
disappears from all of this because
again you can have people signing up
they're getting content but there's no
urgency to actually buy from you and so
what ends up happening in our experience
is the sales end up going way way down
unless you bring back in some of those
mechanisms of urgency and as a coach and
as a mentor you know for years I was
like well I don't I don't want to have
to do that I want to give people the the
autonomy and the agency to decide to
make the decision for themselves but
here's the reality is that most people
are not going to make a decision to
become a client of your simply because
you have value that you offered them you
can literally give value value value
value value so much value that's out
there and trust me I've tried
it and then what but without actually
learning how to be
persuasive
engaging effective at your sales ability
nobody is going to actually buy from you
and here's why because unfortunately we
live in a very unique World in 2024 that
we didn't live in years ago when I got
into this industry 21 years ago we
actually didn't have some of these same
problems it's a lot easier back then and
so a lot of people are going based on
those same strategies that we did 21
years ago now there are some things that
are consistent that are not dead that
are not dying but one of the things that
has changed is people's attention span a
lot of people are being diagnosed with
adult ADHD they don't have the attention
span to consistently watch content the
fact that you've made it 7 minutes into
this video right here a shows that
there's something that I'm talking about
that you're interested in but B it also
shows that you have the ability to
direct your attention at what you
actually care about and so one of the
things is is that we have to realize
that most people are not going to give
us their attention they're not going to
engage with us consistently they're not
going to show up with us us and that's
okay and we have to accept that fact
right out of the gate and there's
literally nothing that you can do in
today's world to change that fact except
for this is that you can learn how to
design what your content is and what
your offer is to become something that
is irresistible for what they really
want you figure out what are the main
pillars of the solution that you offer
right
here and you promise them over here you
make a bold promise of an outcome that
they would have to pay money for to you
and then for that you're able to deliver
that in your content right here now you
might say well if I deliver that in my
content right here what are they going
to pay me for and this becomes the
Dilemma that a lot of people have in
marketing is they're afraid to actually
give their best content away because
they're like what are people going to
actually pay me for but here's the truth
human beings don't actually work that
way human beings work in a very specific
spefic way that when they get shared
something that they would previously
have paid money for and it really really
connects with what they actually
desire the chances of them trusting you
go up exponentially but that's only one
piece of the equation in sales and
marketing trust is the currency of
people becoming your clients and you
have to learn how to build trust with
people you have to learn how to
communicate in a way that builds trust
with people there's a Cadence to it
there's a methodology to doing so and it
Bec comes automatic over time I stunk at
this for years I didn't know how to I
didn't know how to communicate in a way
that did this and I used to complain and
why why I have so much value I'm giving
but nobody is trusting me how many of
you have felt that way before that you
know that you have value that you know
that there's something that you want to
deliver to people but nobody wants to
buy it from you it's exhausting it's
frustrating it's it's not fun it's scary
it's
it's just it's terrible okay let's we
don't need to go deeper into that but
like when you can learn that skill set
and that's something that I coach my
clients on in my client growth
accelerator program is how to have
consistent profits how to dial in their
messaging how to sell effectively how to
attract the right clients to them and
how to get the right people becoming
their clients and listen I'd love for
you to work with me inside of there you
can find a link below as to how to get
more info about that and how to jump
into our accelerator program below this
video in the the description but what
you have to do is you have to learn how
to effectively communicate in a way that
sells to people that gets people to buy
from you and you can't be afraid to sell
in your business it takes two
abilities the ability to get people's
attention and the ability to persuade
them to buy from you so those go twofold
we have to grab their attention with
something they desire if you see a car
that you desire or you know
if you're a single person you see a a
person that you would desire to get to
know or or something like that or you
see a house that you would desire again
I don't mean to objectify people but
when you're single it it's it's hard not
to in some ways you're like I want that
type of person right and so that's
desirable you have a desire in your
business to accomplish something your
clients have a desire to experience
something that you can deliver to them
and so what you do is you bait the hook
with the desire that they have and then
you create an irresistible offer what is
that it means you're packaging it in a
way that is enticing it makes them
salivate when they see it it draws them
in dare I say it it is seductive to what
they desire the most they really
passionately want it it Taps right into
everything they've ever wanted and when
you can learn how to build an offer this
way when you can learn how to
communicate it that way when you can
dial in your messaging that way and your
language and you know how to attract
that through your social media through
advertising campaigns through YouTube
videos to get people to buy from you it
actually becomes very easy to make the
kind of money that you want to make in
our businesses that's exactly what we've
done and that's exactly what I Mentor
people on in my client growth
accelerator program again if you want
that I'd love to work with you in there
I'd love to help you with that you know
we got a special deal going on right now
at the time of this video where we're
going to be actually offering a 14-day
trial to jump into that program and so
listen keep an eye out for that get on
the waiting list for it and I'd love to
work with you in there to help you get
those results when you can learn how to
find what the desire that somebody has
is you can attach that to your lead
magnet right here so what I look at is
what is the value that I'm offering in
my coaching program and then I figure
out what is the thing that somebody
wants the most so I put that together in
the form of a free offer something that
people can get for free from me a video
training of some kind and then when they
watch that video I am guiding people and
leading them through the process of the
value that they're going to get we're
going to be showing them what why they
need to take action now and here's how
you add the urgency and the scarcity
that's missing from Evergreen that
increases those amount of sales because
we don't want reduced sales by going
Evergreen remember I talked about this
if we're doing live your lead magnet
could be a live webinar or a challenge
and that's great and it works and it
produces a lot of sales and it makes a
lot of money but it can be exhausting so
if we want to make it Evergreen we
remove that factor of it being live or
happening on a live day and you
pre-record it you make everything
pre-recorded you got to pre-write the
emails there's a lot more work on the
front end it's a little more um
structured as far as that goes but
it allows you to remove
yourself from the active building of
your business it allows you to remove
yourself from actively being the one
that has to do all of the work in your
business and as you grow you can add
even more mechanisms to it like a Setter
or a closer team members that are able
to even reach out and help you with the
sales process it's amazing to be able to
do this we work with a client that does
this and they make tens of millions of
dollars being able to do this in their
business
so when you can figure out what people
want and you know how to create a video
presentation which we Mentor you with in
my program that keeps people's attention
that is engaging and that effectively
sells to people what your program is now
you can get them to buy from you now we
do all of that when we do it live but
when you go Evergreen again you lose
some of that connection you lose some of
that urgency so the way that we bring it
back in is
this you can create a
limited
offer that is only available inside of
the Evergreen offer so for
instance you have a coaching program
right maybe you have the doors open all
the time your Evergreen offer can offer
a 50% discount that they can only get
when they go through the offer right
there and they can only get it through
that link right there if they come if
they if they and so
they might go back to your website later
and they won't be able to get that it's
the original price but because they
signed up for your Evergreen offer
they're able to get that you can also do
what's called a
deadline
funnel and deadline funnel is actually a
a little piece of code that you put on
your soft on your website and in your
email and what it does is it actually
creates the same kind of urgency that
you would do with a live launch but it
allows you to say oh you have three to
five
days to get this discount now check this
out let's say that somebody came in
after the 5-day discount was over how do
you give them the discount with the 3 to
five days after it comes over well
that's the CH that's the that's the
Dilemma that's the problem that's why
live launching is so effective is
because you're able to get everybody in
you're kind of corralling people into
one place
and then you open the doors and you have
uh and it works really well by the way
it's really effective it's a great way
in your business again I'm not knocking
live launching as a method I think it's
actually like really good it works well
I love it it's how we built my business
to 7 figures however if you want to
remove yourself from your business if
you want to work just 5 to 10 hours a
week if you want to be able to have the
same kind of profits you have to deliver
some of these mechanisms back into it
and and so a deadline funnel allows you
to put this little line of code on there
that tracks when somebody came in and it
does a countdown to the end of the offer
and then it removes the offer from them
so that after those 3 to five days they
don't get the discount or they don't get
the the bonus classes or they they don't
get the the trial period right here you
know in my accelerator program what we I
offer people is I actually offer them
kind of a combination of all this we got
a discount we got a trial period and you
get bonus classes only when you come in
for that but you can only get that for 3
days is what it is and most people if
they visit my website or they even come
through a YouTube video they don't get
that and we might not offer that in the
future and
so the way that we structure this is to
add back in that
urgency so that when somebody comes in
to your ecosystem when they join your
funnel
you get to say okay sign up before this
date and time and then you get to get
this bonus you get to try things out you
get this discount and that increases
dramatically the amount of people that
buy from you and here's the problem you
don't want to be dishonest using
deadline funnel makes you honest which
is awesome because it's it it tracks
perfectly to who the person is when they
came in it tracks it right to their
email address so it goes right to their
email address and they can only come in
through that to be able to buy from you
and this is why I love this is because
you can use a lot of the great different
tools that we do like Instagram ads like
Facebook ads like many chat funnels like
uh organic social media content like
email marketing like long form videos
like this and you can lead everybody to
your limited
offer and they can all come in at
different dates and times it's different
moments but you're able to say that it's
still
limited there's expiring bonuses there's
a time when it's going to
stop and this allows you to get more
sales from people and I found this is
that without that urgency added to it of
some kind with either bonuses or things
like
that the chances of people buying from
you are pretty small they're pretty low
even if your offer is amazing there's a
there's a there's a number of other
people that are out there that are
offering incredible things to people and
most people just are not ready to take
action with you they're not ready to
jump in with you simply just because you
have something amazing to offer you
might be watching this right now you
might be saying yeah well but my program
is so unique it's so different from
everything else that's out there can I
tell you this how how's your sales going
how many sales are you
making most people that are watching
this right now you're going to answer
I'm not making the kind of sales that I
want to make I'm not making any
sales and so as somebody who's been in
this industry for years I'm telling you
that this is the best way to be able to
remove yourself from your business to
not have to have a lot of staff to be
able to be a solopreneur to work only 10
to 15 hours a week and still be able to
get the kind of clients that you want to
make and so listen if you want to know
how to dial in your offer if you want to
know all the technical aspects of
building a funnel like this if you want
to work with me to become a part of your
team to help you put all this together
I'd love to do so in my accelerator
program that's exactly what I do with my
clients every single week is help them
get results in their businesses and I
can help you with that as well all right
so listen stay plugged in subscribe to
the channel keep watching our videos and
start creating the kind of business that
you want to make you can design your
business based on how you want it to
look how you want it to be you don't
have to struggle you don't have to
stress out you don't have to burn out
you don't have to work 100 hours a week
you can have the type of life that you
want to live that's your dream life and
I can help you get there we'll talk soon
everybody have a good one